famouswhy.com 2016-10-29

# FamousWhy: Privacy Policy

2 April, 2009

**Privacy**

You can visit FamousWhy.com without revealing who you are or any information about yourself. 

There are times, however, when the FamousWhy.com or its Members ("We" or "Us") may need information from you. 

You may choose to give personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you. We intend to let you know how such information will be used before it is collected from you on the Internet. 

If you tell Us that you do not want Us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, We will respect your wishes.

**Information Security and Quality :**

**What information of yours does the FamousWhy.com collect?**

Our goal is to become your favorite Internet destination by providing the information, services, and product offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, the FamousWhy.com must collect information so we can understand what makes you different from its millions of other unique users. 

While you are not required to register for any services on the FamousWhy.com.

Information collected online is usually defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable. 

FamousWhy collects anonymous information, which refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual.

For example, FamousWhy.com collects some information each time a visitor comes to site so we can improve the overall quality of the visitor's online experience. FamousWhy.com collects the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from ibm.com or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to www.FamousWhy.com), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). FamousWhy.com also collects aggregate search terms from its search services for internal reporting targeted advertising, and the FamousWhy.com of popular search terms. FamousWhy.com collects this user information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. In addition, FamousWhy.com collects your responses to online surveys displayed on the FamousWhy.com Network; these anonymous and optional surveys will seek your opinions about the Products and Services or the advertisements displayed on FamousWhy.com. 

You do not have to register with the www.FamousWhy.com before we can collect this anonymous information. 

Personally identifiable information refers to data that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and postal address, which may be collected in addition to the anonymous data described above.

**What are "cookies" and "Web beacons" and how does FamousWhy.com use them?**

In addition to the personally identifiable information that FamousWhy.com actively collects when you register, we also collect anonymous information passively using cookies and Web beacons. This technology plays an important role in making the Internet work, but there is much confusion among Internet users about what cookies and Web beacons are and how they are used. 

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a Web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the Web site. This unique number identifies your Web browser to our computer system whenever you visit one of the sites in the FamousWhy.com Network. A cookie will not allow a Web site to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed.

Cookies allow FamousWhy.com to automatically remember your Web browser when you visit our Network of Web sites. 

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major Web sites. 

It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. While FamousWhy.com does not require you to use cookies, keep in mind that certain sites and services will not function properly if you set your browser to refuse all cookies. 

**What Are Web Beacons?**

A Web beacon is clear GIF (Graphics Interchange Format) image that often appears invisible because it is only one by one pixel in size. Typically, Web beacons are created using HTML (HyperText Markup Language) tags in Web page code. We employ Web beacons on Web sites, on behalf of our clients, to help them analyze and measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns and the general usage patterns of visitors to their Web sites. 

For example, when a user clicks on an advertiser's Internet ad, the user is taken to the advertiser's Web page. If the advertiser chooses to employ a Web beacon, the advertiser's Web page will contain a clear GIF image that is not visible on your screen. The Web beacon typically would be used by the advertiser to collect certain anonymous information about your visit to a particular Web site. This Non-PII is sent to the advertiser's ad server for processing. 

**How Can Users Block Cookies?**

One way you can stop cookies from being stored on your computer, and therefore, stop Web sites and advertisers from storing and using anonymous information collected about you, is to block all cookies by disabling cookies in your Internet browser configuration. This will block cookies from our clients and everybody else. 

Depending on your Internet browser, you can block all cookies in the following way:

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.x

1\. Menu: Tools-Internet Options

2\. Select Tab: Privacy

3\. Pull "slider" to "Block All Cookies," which is the highest setting

Netscape Navigator 4.x

1\. Menu: Edit-Preferences

2\. Select Category: Advanced

3\. Find section: Cookies

4\. Select your choice 

**How Can Users Delete Cookies?**

One way you can delete cookies stored on your computer, and therefore interrupt the process by which Web sites and advertisers collect anonymous information about you, is to delete all cookies on your computer's hard drive. This will delete cookies from our clients and everybody else. Depending on your Internet browser, you can delete all cookies in the following way:

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.x

1\. Menu: Tools-Internet Options

2\. Select Tab: Settings

3\. Select Tab: View Files

4\. Select and delete the cookies you want to delete from your hard drive. 

Netscape Navigator 4.x

1\. Menu: Edit-Preferences

2\. Select Category: Advanced

3\. Find section: Cookies

4\. Select your choice 

**CAUTION REGARDING LINKED WEB SITES.**

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked Web sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**  
About Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:** \- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.famouswhy.com  
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- As a user, you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  

\----------------------------------------

**Notification of Changes**

This privacy statement was last updated on April 2, 2009.
